

EDUCATION

2022

Designboat UI/UX School, (Certified) Bangalore, India

2015-2020

B.Arch, Department of Architecture, Anna University, Chennai, India

SKILLS

Software	Design
Figma	UX Research
Sketch	Qualitative Analysis
Adobe XD	Quantitative Analysis
Invision	UX Design
Framer	Market Research
SketchUp 3D	Web/Mobile Design
Adobe Photoshop	Wireframing
Adobe Illustrator	UI Design
Adobe Indesign	Prototype & Test

Programming

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

JavaScript

LANGUAGES

English - Fluent

Tamil - Native

Hindi - Intermediate

(curious to learn more)

GEERTHIKA LAKSHMANAN

UI/UX Designer

Tamilnadu 630301, India

argeerthi14@gmail.com

+91 9095232109

LinkedIn | Behance

Portfolio Link:

www.geerthika.com

ABOUT

A blend of UI/UX and Architecture. With 2+ years of experience in design field, My expertise has been in E-commerce, WEB 3.0 Blockchain Industry, HealthCare, Fintech products - with IOS, Android & Website Design. Knowledge of HTML5, CSS3 and JS with respect to design. Communication and team play has always been my strength. I'm open to relocation for the right opportunity.

EXPERIENCE

UX UI Designer (Oct 2022 - Present)

GeekyAnts, Bangalore - Product company, Experience in UX Design Design system, Stakeholder interviews, Competitive Analysis, Qualitative Analysis, Quantitative Analysis, UsabilityTesting. Interaction with PM's and stakeholders.

User Experience Designer (June 2022 - August 2022)

Redd Experience Design (Company Merged) - B2C Worked on the crypto web projects, I contributed to the task of redesigning the marketing collaterals for the brand Persistence One with UX Research, Information Architecture, prototype and Interface Design including the pitch deck, BNB Deck, and PStake.

UI UX Designer (June 2021 - May 2022)

Freelance Designer B2B - Worked on products from design thinking process, UX Rsearch, QA research, Persona, Journey maps, workshops, User flow, competitive research, Market study, wireframe and clickable prototype. Collaboration with startups in Storyboard, Colour psychology and Social media management.

Junior Designer (Jan 2020 - Oct 2021)

HCP design Planning & Management pvt.ltd, Ahmedabad - Worked on the project of 'Central Vista Redevelopment of India, Delhi'.

Communication and Visual Design - Indian government presentation deliverables. Mock-ups, design guidelines and specifications.

Internship (June 2018 - March 2019)

SR+A Architects, Mumbai - Architecture Internship